{
    "id": "eee1baddcec14dc387229505570ed878",
    "title": "Adjectives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The elephant is a large animal. The rabbit is a ................................. animal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "small",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "38d21a93962f4afcbf147e738fb48585"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is cold in winter. It is ....................................... in summer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hot",
                "heated"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bdfaf37ac31a439fbe293ffc1b9fcd85"
        },
        {
            "question": "Yesterday it was cloudy. Today is a ................................. day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sun",
                "sunny"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "26995b7efa504fa5b3184fec017b5258"
        },
        {
            "question": "These shirts are wet. Haven’t you got a ....................................... one?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dry",
                "dried"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6dcf99999f884371863019d12e3a6739"
        },
        {
            "question": "We won’t reach there in time if we go by a slow train. We must catch a .................................... train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "faster",
                "fast"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "094c415c9c504ce5abd31bb4cac77982"
        },
        {
            "question": "My shoes are old. I want to buy a .................................. pair.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "new",
                "fresh"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6de0eaa20cdc477da1e8e4ac6af4f171"
        },
        {
            "question": "Some colors are bright. Others are ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "black",
                "pale",
                "dark"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3713c41371304270a17940f797ee3c20"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is warm outside. It is ....................................... inside.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cool",
                "cooled"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6ad826e549c644d8b3a40807c30e26ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "This bread is stale. We must buy a ................................ loaf.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "new",
                "fresh"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "adc2cd7d99a341da9a6a6371b7986fe8"
        },
        {
            "question": "This knife is blunt. I need a .................................. one.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "keen",
                "sharp"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2b895724149c4b5f94a5c33b9972558e"
        }
    ]
}